ltheme.com 2018-10-13

# Privacy Policy - Responsive Joomla and Wordpress themes

Privacy Policy

3 (60%) 2 votes 

**Personally identifiable information**  
Only information you provide _LTheme_ with directly will be collected, such as through subscribing to various products & services, or identifying yourself when requesting information to be sent to you. For example, when you fill out a request form, we collect the details you enter in order to post information to you. When you answer questions about what you would like to see we keep this information so as to better serve you.

**Emails**  
From time to time with your permission LTheme will send you relevant information emails regarding products and services which you have previously registered your interest in. If you are receiving promotional information from LTheme and do not wish to receive this information any longer, you may unsubscribe anytime.

**Cookies**  
_LTheme_ uses “cookies” to help enhance your experience on the site. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Most Web browsers are set to accept cookies as the default. Cookies themselves do not contain personal information about you. They simply operate as a unique identifier which helps JoomlaShine to know what customers find interesting and useful on the website, almost like a continuing questionnaire. JoomlaShine does not store any personal information inside cookies, although the cookie may identify the user’s browser.  
The use of cookies can enhance your experience on the _LTheme_ site, by remembering information that you have previously given. They can make it easier for you to fill out forms, shop online and can ensure that information provided to you is most relevant to your interests.

**Log files**  
We and/or our contracted web analytic provider(s) do keep track of the domains from which you access our Site and Services on the World Wide Web, and may log IP addresses or other identifiers for statistical purposes. We do this to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use to identify and analyze trends and the results of our marketing efforts, to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer the Site and Services, and analyze users’ movements. We may periodically share aggregate demographic information with our business partners. IP addresses and other identifiers are not linked to personally identifiable information.
